https://www.dpzarchitects.com/privacy/

Skip to content
PrivacyAndrew Quarrie2020-06-01T15:37:43-04:00Faring Well By DesignA global pandemic is the type of resiliency test we plan for, but hope never occurs. We are happy to report that amidst the current difficulties, our compact, walkable, mixed-use, and multigenerational communities are not only faring well but are proving to be a source of comfort to their residents as they shelter in place.IntroductionThese terms and conditions govern your use of this website; by using this website, you accept these terms and conditions in full. If you disagree with these terms and conditions or any part of these terms and conditions, you must not use this website.This website uses cookies.  By using this website and agreeing to these terms and conditions, you consent to DPZ CoDesign, LLC’s use of cookies in accordance with the terms of DPZ CoDesign, LLC’s privacy policy.License to Use Website
Unless otherwise stated, DPZ CoDesign, LLC and/or its licensors own the intellectual property rights in the website and material on the website.  Subject to the license below, all these intellectual property rights are reserved.You may view, download for caching purposes only, and print pages from the website for your own personal use, subject to the restrictions set out below and elsewhere in these terms and conditions.You must not:republish material from this website (including republication on another website);sell, rent or sub-license material from the website;show any material from the website in public;reproduce, duplicate, copy or otherwise exploit material on this website for a commercial purpose;redistribute material from this website, except for content specifically and expressly made available for redistribution and with prior arrangement.Acceptable UseYou must not use this website in any way that causes, or may cause, damage to the website or impairment of the availability or accessibility of the website; or in any way which is unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful, or in connection with any unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful purpose or activity. You must not use this website to copy, store, host, transmit, send, use, publish or distribute any material which consists of (or is linked to) any spyware, computer virus, Trojan horse, worm, keystroke logger, rootkit or other malicious computer software.You must not conduct any systematic or automated data collection activities (including without limitation scraping, data mining, data extraction and data harvesting) on or in relation to this website without DPZ CoDesign, LLC ’s express written consent.You must not use this website to transmit or send unsolicited commercial communications.Restricted AccessAccess to certain areas of this website is restricted. DPZ CoDesign, LLC reserves the right to restrict access to areas of this website, or indeed this entire website, at DPZ CoDesign, LLC’s discretion.If DPZ CoDesign, LLC provides you with a user ID and password to enable you to access restricted areas of this website or other content or services, you must ensure that the user ID and password are kept confidential.DPZ CoDesign, LLC may disable your user ID and password in DPZ CoDesign, LLC’s sole discretion without notice or explanation.User ContentIn these terms and conditions, “your user content” means material (including without limitation text, images, audio material, video material and audio-visual material) that you submit to this website, for whatever purpose.You grant to DPZ CoDesign, LLC a worldwide, irrevocable, non-exclusive, royalty-free license to use, reproduce, adapt, publish, translate and distribute your user content in any existing or future media.  You also grant to DPZ CoDesign, LLC the right to sub-license these rights, and the right to bring an action for infringement of these rights.Your user content must not be illegal or unlawful, must not infringe any third party’s legal rights, and must not be capable of giving rise to legal action whether against you or DPZ CoDesign, LLC or a third party (in each case under any applicable law).You must not submit any user content to the website that is or has ever been the subject of any threatened or actual legal proceedings or other similar complaint.DPZ CoDesign, LLC reserves the right to edit or remove any material submitted to this website, or stored on its servers, or hosted or published upon this website.No WarrantiesThis website is provided “as is” without any representations or warranties, express or implied. DPZ CoDesign, LLC makes no representations or warranties in relation to this website or the information and materials provided on this website.Without prejudice to the generality of the foregoing paragraph, DPZ CoDesign, LLC does not warrant that:this website will be constantly available, or available at all;or the information on this website is complete, true, accurate or non-misleading.Nothing on this website constitutes, or is meant to constitute, advice of any kind.Limitations of LiabilityDPZ CoDesign, LLC will not be liable to you (whether under the law of contact, the law of torts or otherwise) in relation to the contents of, or use of, or otherwise in connection with, this website:to the extent that the website is provided free-of-charge, for any direct loss;for any indirect, special or consequential loss; orfor any business losses, loss of revenue, income, profits or anticipated savings, loss of contracts or business relationships, loss of reputation or goodwill, or loss or corruption of information or data.DPZ CoDesign, LLC will not be liable for any user-generated content (comments, images, videos, audio, or any other content format posted by users) and any harm it may cause.ExceptionsNothing in this website disclaimer will exclude or limit any warranty implied by law that it would be unlawful to exclude or limit; and nothing in this website disclaimer will exclude or limit DPZ CoDesign, LLC ’s liability in respect of any:death or personal injury caused by negligence;fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation on the part of DPZ CoDesign, LLC ; or matter which it would be illegal or unlawful for DPZCoDesign, LLC to exclude or limit, or to attempt or purport to exclude or limit, its liability.ReasonablenessBy using this website, you agree that the exclusions and limitations of liability set out in this website disclaimer are reasonable. If you do not think they are reasonable, you must not use this website.Other PartiesYou agree that the limitations of warranties and liability set out in this website disclaimer will protect DPZ CoDesign, LLC ’s officers, employees, agents, subsidiaries, successors, assigns and sub-contractors.IndemnityYou hereby indemnify DPZ CoDesign, LLC and undertake to keep DPZ CoDesign, LLC indemnified against any losses, damages, costs, liabilities and expenses (including without limitation legal expenses and any amounts paid by DPZ CoDesign, LLC to a third party in settlement of a claim or dispute on the advice of DPZ CoDesign, LLC legal advisers) incurred or suffered by DPZ CoDesign, LLC arising out of any breach by you of any provision of these terms and conditions, or arising out of any claim that you have breached any provision of these terms and conditions.Breach of Terms and ConditionsWithout prejudice to DPZ CoDesign, LLC ’s other rights under these terms and conditions, if you breach these terms and conditions in any way, DPZ CoDesign, LLC may take such action as DPZ CoDesign, LLC deems appropriate to deal with the breach, including suspending your access to the website, prohibiting you from accessing the website, blocking computers using your IP address from accessing the website, contacting your internet service provider to request that they block your access to the website and/or bringing court proceedings against you.VariationDPZ CoDesign, LLC may revise these terms and conditions from time-to-time.  Revised terms and conditions will apply to the use of this website from the date of the publication of the revised terms and conditions on this website.  Please check this page regularly to ensure you are familiar with the current version.AssignmentDPZ CoDesign, LLC may transfer, sub-contract or otherwise deal with DPZ CoDesign, LLC ’s rights and/or obligations under these terms and conditions without notifying you or obtaining your consent. You may not transfer, sub-contract or otherwise deal with your rights and/or obligations under these terms and conditions.SeverabilityIf a provision of these terms and conditions is determined by any court or other competent authority to be unlawful and/or unenforceable, the other provisions will continue in effect.  If any unlawful and/or unenforceable provision would be lawful or enforceable if part of it were deleted, that part will be deemed to be deleted, and the rest of the provision will continue in effect.Entire AgreementThese terms and conditions, together with the Privacy Policy, constitute the entire agreement between you and DPZ CoDesign, LLC in relation to your use of this website, and supersede all previous agreements in respect of your use of this website.Law and JurisdictionThese terms and conditions will be governed by and construed in accordance with United States law, and any disputes relating to these terms and conditions will be subject to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of the State of Florida and of the United States.Registrations and AuthorizationsDPZ CoDesign, LLC and all associated marks, content, images and intellectual property are the wholly-owned property of DPZ CoDesign, LLC. You can contact DPZ CoDesign, LLC by email to hello@dpz.comPRIVACY POLICYYour privacy is important to DPZ CoDesign, LLC. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that DPZ CoDesign, LLC collects, and the ways in which DPZ CoDesign, LLC uses that personal information.Personal information collectionDPZ CoDesign, LLC may collect and use the following kinds of information:Information about your use of DPZ CoDesign, LLC website, including pages visited, time on site, sharing of content, commenting and discussion activity, event registration, signing up and changing your e-mail preferences, registering for memberships and changing your member information.Information that you used for registering on the website, including your name, e-mail address, username, and password.Information that you used for conducting transactions on DPZ CoDesign, LLC website, such as registering for membership or paid events, including credit card and billing information.Any other information that you send to DPZ CoDesign, LLC .Third-party software and integrationsDPZ CoDesign, LLC may use third-party services to help improve our process for serving our clients and community. By using the DPZ CoDesign, LLC website, you agree to the terms of service and privacy policy of all such third-party software and service integration into DPZ CoDesign, LLC’s website.DPZ CoDesign, LLC will not be liable for any harm caused by the use of third-party software integrations into DPZ CoDesign, LLC’s website.Using personal informationDPZ CoDesign, LLC may use your personal information to:Administer DPZ CoDesign, LLC website or newsletterPersonalize the website or newsletter for you and provide you with particular contentEnable you to access and use certain parts of or services on the websitePublish information about you on the websiteSend you products and tickets that you purchaseSend you receipts, confirmations, and billing noticesCollect payments from youSend you marketing information and materialsContact you via e-mailWhere DPZ CoDesign, LLC discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, DPZ CoDesign, LLC may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.Securing your dataDPZ CoDesign, LLC will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.DPZ CoDesign, LLC will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.Information relating to electronic transactions conducted via DPZ CoDesign, LLC website will be  protected by encryption technology.Cross-border data transfersInformation that DPZ CoDesign, LLC collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which DPZ CoDesign, LLC operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.Updating this statementDPZ CoDesign, LLC may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on its website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.Other websitesDPZ CoDesign, LLC website contains links to other websites. DPZ CoDesign, LLC is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.Contact DPZ CoDesign, LLC
DPZ CoDesign, LLC and all associated marks, content, and intellectual property are wholly owned by DPZ CoDesign, LLC . If you have any questions about this privacy policy or DPZ CoDesign, LLC’s treatment of your personal information, please write by email to hello@dpz.com
Go to Top
